{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}